<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jonas Bučinskas</title>
    <link>https://bucinskas.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jonas Bučinskas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2023, Jonas Bučinskas</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 23:02:14 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bucinskas.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What to expect from Founder.University?</title>
      <link>https://bucinskas.io/posts/founder-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 23:02:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bucinskas.io/posts/founder-university/</guid>
      <description>What to expect from Founder.University? My co-founder Ignas and I just wrapped up a 12-week Founder.University pre-accelerator programme. Putting this blog post in the books primarily for ourselves, so we could share it out the next time someone asks us &amp;ldquo;Should I join Founder Uni?&amp;rdquo;.
Hint: You should!
What is Founder.University? Founder University (FU for short) will teach you how to start a technology company. It&amp;rsquo;s a 12-week pre-accelerator for startups that is run by Kelly and Presh, and is part of a larger LAUNCH venture investment firm/accelerator headed by none other than Jason Calacanis himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>README / User Manual</title>
      <link>https://bucinskas.io/posts/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 15:49:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bucinskas.io/posts/readme/</guid>
      <description>README / User Manual Interested in creating your own user manual? Check out this article
Last update: Oct 20, 2023
About Usually, I revisit this document once a year. I&amp;rsquo;m always surprised to see how my approach to product and now company development has evolved. Every year I learn something new and in a lot of cases those learnings are about things that I should stop doing or pay attention to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaunas Has the Audacity</title>
      <link>https://bucinskas.io/posts/kaunas-has-the-audacity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 13:35:53 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bucinskas.io/posts/kaunas-has-the-audacity/</guid>
      <description>Kaunas Has the Audacity A few years ago I was about an hour away from boarding a flight to New York when a stranger in front of me just plainly asked &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s happening in Kaunas in 2022?&amp;rdquo;. Honestly, it threw me off a little until I realized I was wearing a T-Shirt with &amp;ldquo;Kaunas 2022&amp;rdquo; written all over it. After quickly gathering my thoughts, I launched into a pitch.
I talked about what the European Capital of Culture is, how every year a few new cities take the title, what it means, and how Kaunas is going to be different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building products the right way</title>
      <link>https://bucinskas.io/posts/building-the-right-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:32:09 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bucinskas.io/posts/building-the-right-way/</guid>
      <description>I love experimentation, iteration, creating proofs of concept. I, also, strongly believe that any code that is not in production is completely useless. That being said, as a person who ships software products for a living, the #1 struggle I have is launching something that is “good enough”.
Product launch that is “good enough” really means that:
“We just launched something that meets some baseline expectations of our potential buyers who use similar products already”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
